https://lucascapital.com/privacy-policy/

Our Commitment
Why Lucas Capital?
Why Lucas Capital?
Our Commitment
Why Lucas Capital?
Why Lucas Capital?
Privacy Policy
The privacy practices of this Privacy Policy apply to our services available under the domain and subdomains of www.lucascapital.com (the “Website”). We recognize that privacy is important to our users, so we design and operate our Website with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we may gather when you visit our Website or use our services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which we protect, use and disclose your personal information.
By visiting the Website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use or access the Website.
By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy is effective when accepted by new users, and is otherwise effective on July 31, 2008, for all users.
Overview
We have adopted general policies and procedures concerning confidentiality, proprietary data, and privacy of customer personal information, and the information we gather over the Website is protected by those policies and procedures. Generally, we collect non-public personal information about our clients and investors from the following sources:
Information received from clients or investors on applications or other forms, including the information we collect on the Website, and
Information about clients’ or investors’ transactions with us, our affiliates or others.
Our policy is that:
We do not disclose any non-public personal information about our current or former clients or investors to anyone, except as permitted by law. We share non-public personal information with certain service providers, to the extent permitted by law, and we require those service providers to keep the non-public information confidential.
We restrict access to non-public personal information about our clients and investors to employees and service providers who need to know that information to provide services to our clients.
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard clients’ and investors’ personal information.
Collection of Information
In general, you can browse the non-password-protected sections of the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We automatically track certain information that your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language and one or more files that may uniquely identify your browser. We may use this information to do internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our clients. This information may include the URL from which you just came (whether this URL is on the Website or not), to which URL you next go (whether this URL is on the Website or not), your computer browser information and your IP address. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.
We also may use data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain pages of the Website to help analyze our web page flow, measure effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. “Cookies” are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a “cookie”. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are “session cookies,” meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on the Website and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session. We use cookies to better understand how people interact with us.
If you apply for a password to access password-restricted areas on this Website, you must provide to us your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, personal financial data, investment portfolio, and other investment information.
Use and Disclosure of Information
We use the information we collect from our browser and data collection devices such as cookies to improve our operations and facilitate the services you request. We may use information collected from you to measure interest, customize your experience and enforce our Terms of Use. If you apply for a password, we use that data to determine whether you are an accredited investor and have sufficient sophistication, investment experience and wealth to receive information about certain investment options. We may use your information to send correspondence and perform services on your behalf in connection with investment-related activities.
You agree that we may use personal information about you to analyze Website usage, improve our content and product offerings and customize the Website’s content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Website and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Website.
In connection with providing our services, it also may be necessary for us to share information with other third parties to help us process transactions relating to your account, including, but not limited to, asset transfers from a financial institution and processing or administering investment transactions and portfolios. In certain instances, we may contract with third parties that are not affiliated with us to perform services for us, and, if necessary, we may disclose information about you to those third parties solely for the purpose of carrying out their assigned responsibilities. In those circumstances, we require such third parties to treat your private information with the same degree of confidentiality that we do. In some instances, the third-party service provider may collect information directly from you. In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the service provider, and all additional information you provide them and their additional uses will be strictly up to you. If you provide additional information to a service provider directly, their use of your personal information is governed by their applicable privacy policy.
We may also share information about you if we believe that disclosure is required under the law. For example, we may need to disclose information in response to a subpoena or to cooperate with regulatory or law enforcement authorities.
We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not described in this Privacy Policy. For example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or service providers may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Website. Therefore, although we use industry-standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.
Security
Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We use procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, which may include encryption, “firewalls” and Secure Socket Layers. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet.
Children
Persons under age 18 are not eligible to use the Website.
Conditions Of Use
If you choose to visit the Website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of New Jersey. If you have any concerns about privacy, please send a thorough description to mbglaccum@lucascapital.com.
Changes to this policy
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Website. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Website.
If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us any time at mbglaccum@lucascapital.com.
Why Lucas Capital?
Lucas Capital Management, L.L.C. ("LCM") is an investment adviser registered with the SEC. LCM's
website is limited to the dissemination of general information regarding LCM's investment
advisory services. The information on this website is for general informational purposes only
and should not be construed by any prospective or existing client of LCM as a solicitation to
effect transactions in securities. In addition, the information on this website should not be
construed by any prospective or existing client of LCM as personalized investment advice. LCM's
personalized investment advice is given only within the context of its contractual agreements
with each client. LCM's investment advice may only be rendered after the delivery of its Form
ADV-Part II and the execution of an agreement by the client and LCM. LCM's Form ADV-Part II
describes LCM's business operations, services and fees and is available upon request. All
information contained on this website is subject to change without notice. The information
contained on this website may include forward looking statements which are based on LCM's
current opinions, expectations and projections. LCM does not have any obligation to update or
revise any forward looking statements. Actual results could differ materially from those
anticipated in the forward looking statements.
Follow on Social:
Copyright © 2020, Lucas Capital Management. All rights reserved.
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
